<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>joshbergman.io</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on joshbergman.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© [Josh Bergman](https://joshbergman.io)</copyright><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, My name is Josh Bergman. I am a Platform Engineer with 7+ years of experience in AWS and Automation. I have worked in AWS cloud for more than 10 years using Ansible, StackStorm, Terraform, Salt, CloudFormation and Jenkins to create Infrastructure as code in bitbucket. For a list of my full skillset, please visit my skills page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of the projects I have worked on.
Predator Detection System This was created as a scienxce project to deter predators from attacking animals or pets.
Predator Detection
Digital trading card system (In Progress) This was created as an Innovation Project for FIRST Lego League Rototics. The objective was to create a 3D immersive digital trading card system. We used design boards, javascript, CSS and html to create the basis of the app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>Joshua Bergman Highly motivated professional with over 20 years experience in diverse and dynamic environments. Proven ability to deliver high-quality results, meet deadlines and exceed expectations. Skilled in advanced technology and application development. Strong team player and communicator, with a demonstrated ability to collaborate effectively with colleagues.
EXPERIENCE Apiture, Wilmington NC | Remote Platform Engineer III
July 2019 - November 2024
Creating automation workflows to streamline processes and infrastructure as code with Terraform, CloudFormation, Jenkins and Bitbucket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/skills/</guid>
      <description>Languages YAML ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ HCL ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ Bash ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ CloudFormation ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ Python ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ Javascript ✅ ✅ Golang ✅ Typescript ✅ Automation Ansible ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ Terraform ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ StackStorm ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ Jenkins ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ Salt ✅ ✅ ✅ Operating Systems MacOS ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ Linux ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ Windows ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ AWS Cloud EC2 ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ EC2 Security Groups Load Balancers Target Groups S3 ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ Lambda ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ Secrets Manager ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ Secrets Replicas SSM ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ Parameter Store Run command Documents ECS ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ Clusters Services Tasks Backup Service ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ Vaults Jobs Cross Region VPC ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ ✅ </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/robotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/robotics/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
